35 millimeter slides
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 19 [South America], circa 1972; 19 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City buildings], 8
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: View of ocean and palm trees], 9
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Benches], 10
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: A wired lift leading to the top of a mountain], 11
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Doorway?], 12
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City], 13
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Room decorated with murals], 14
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Hotel that says "Caracas Hilton"], 15
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lady sitting in restaurant], 16
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: "Christ the Redeemer" statue in the distance], 17
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City at night], 18
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: "Christ the Redeemer" statue], 19
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City at night], 20
  - Carousel number 19 [South America], circa 1972; 20 (Box 1586)
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: View from top of a mountain, city below], 1
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Stadium], 2
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City and ocean], 3
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas and woman standing on balcony overlooking ocean], 4
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: People on beach], 5
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: People on beach], 6
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: People on beach], 7
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Land, city in distance], 8
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Stone engraved with "Embassy of The United States of America. President Dwight D. Eisenhower. February 23, 1960"], 9
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Parking lot], 10
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Abstract statues of two people], 11
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Abstract statues of two people], 12
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Inside of a theatre], 13
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: A nursery], 14
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Flowering tree], 15
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at a table with a woman], 16
  Box 1587
- 35 millimeter slides, 2.1.5.1
  - Carousel number 19 (continued from previous box) [South America], circa 1972; 1 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City at night], 1
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Building], 2
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Horse-drawn cart], 3
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Abstract statue of two people with bulidings in background at dusk], 4
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City at night [dusk (?)]], 5
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City [Plaza with interesting architecture] at night], 6
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Driving in a car], 7
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Inside of a building], 8
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: City at night], 9
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: [Vasp] Airplane on runway], 10
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: [Vasp] Airplane on runway], 11
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Looking out airplane window, land below], 12
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Waterfalls], 13
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Waterfalls], 14
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Statues of men], 15
    - [Carousel number 19 [South America]: Waterfall], 16
  - Carousel number 20 [South America], circa 1972; 2 (Box 1587)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 20 [South America] [: Large white building with garden in front], 1
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Large white building], 2
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Waterfalls], 3
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Boats on water, city to the right], 4
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: White, domed building], 5
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: White, domed building in a city square], 6
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Hand made rugs on display], 7
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Statue [Bust (?)] of a man], 8
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: City street], 9
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Person riding a donkey under the shade of a sun umbrella], 10
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Market set-up on sidewalk], 11
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: White, domed building (church?)], 12
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of land, jet engine], 13
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Statue of man on a horse], 14
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Large white building], 15
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of mountains], 16
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of mountains], 17
  - Carousel number 20 [South America], circa 1972; 3 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Poverty striken people sitting outside of run-down building], 1
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Park], 2
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Statue of a woman; "Mabel La Catolica"], 3
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Wild llama (alpaca?)], 4
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Farmland], 5
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Street band playing music], 6
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Sign in Spanish. Name on sign, "Don Ronald B. Clark"], 7
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: View of ocean and mountains], 8
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Wild llama (alpaca?)], 9
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at picnic tables, a dog lying at their feet], 10
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at picnic table], 11
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at picnic table with a dog lying at her feet], 12
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas with another woman, at picnic tables with a dog lying at their feet], 13
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting at picnic table with dog lying at her feet, Lowell Thomas looking at ocean view, another man standing nearby them], 14
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A model boat], 15
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Market set-up on dirt road], 16
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Market set-up on dirt road], 17
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A stone bridge, statue of a man riding on a horse], 18
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a restaurant], 19
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another woman sitting in a restaurant], 20
  - Carousel number 20 [South America], circa 1972; 4 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of land, jet engine], 1
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of land], 2
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of ocean], 3
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of ocean and city], 4
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of ocean and city], 5
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Aerial view of ocean and land], 6
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A city street], 7
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A fountain], 8
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Statue of a man riding a horse], 9
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A fountain], 10
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Old fashioned horse drawn carriage on display], 11
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Courtyard of a building], 12
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Traffic on a city street], 13
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Historical artifacts], 14
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: A grand building], 15
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Man standing near a llama (alpaca?)], 16
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Barren land [Desert with mountain in background (?)], 17
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: City street], 18
  - Carousel number 20 [South America] [Items 1-4] Carousel number 21 [Items 5-20], circa 1972; 5 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Top of fort or armory, cannon at the left], 1
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas next to a llama (alpaca?)], 2
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Frances Ryan Thomas next to a llama (alpaca?)], 3
    - [Carousel number 20 [South America]: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another woman standing on a snowy road], 4
    - Beginning of Carousel number 21 [American West] [: Lowell Thomas, Frances Ryan Thomas, and another woman standing on a snowy road], 5
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: City], 6
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Fish in a pond], 7
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Fish in a pond], 8
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: LowellThomas standing in front of rock formed into an archway], 9
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Two woman looking at rock formed into an archway], 10
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting together], 11
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Two people sitting together], 12
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of land], 13
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Lowell Thomas standing with another man in a parking lot], 14
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Body of water], 15
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of land], 16
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of canyon (Grand Canyon?)], 17
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of land], 18
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Large building], 19
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of land], 20
  - Carousel number 21 [American West], circa 1972; 6 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Native Americans performing dance], 1
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Native American ceremony], 2
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Large historic stone building], 3
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Woman sitting in airplane], 4
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of mountains], 5
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Lowell Thomas standing in front of building that says "Grand Canyon"], 6
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Lowell Thomas next to airplane], 7
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Man sitting in cockpit of plane], 8
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of city], 9
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Grand Canyon], 10
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Boat on water], 11
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Rock formed into archway], 12
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Aerial view of land], 13
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Domed building], 14
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: Inside of domed building], 15
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: View from airplane, sky], 16
    - [Carousel number 21 [American West]: House], 17
  - Carousel number 22 [Europe; California], circa 1971; 7 (Box 1587)
    - Beginning of Carousel number 22 [Europe; California] [: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in reclining chairs], 1
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Body of water near city], 2
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: People on a boat], 3
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing together], 4
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in chair], 5
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Cabin on a ship], 6
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Looking out of porthole on a ship], 7
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Line of chairs for a waiting area], 8
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas sitting in a restaurant], 9
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Hallway on a cruise ship], 10
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [View from a ship of a boat on the water], 11
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: View of land from a ship], 12
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Street], 13
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Big Ben], 14
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Boat at dock], 15
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Officer on horse], 16
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [London (?)City street], 17
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Tower], 18
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace], 19
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace], 20
  - Carousel number 22 [Europe; California], circa 1971; 8 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace], 1
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace], 2
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace], 3
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Queen Victoria Memorial] Golden angel statue in London], 4
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Queen Victoria Memorial] Golden angel statue in London], 5
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham palace], 6
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City street], 7
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Queen Victoria Memorial] Golden angel statue in London], 8
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Queen Victoria Memorial] Golden angel statue in London], 9
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City street [Theatre Royal Dury Lane]], 10
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City street], 11
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Building], 12
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: High ceiling of a cathedral, Interior of Westminster Abbey], 13
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas walking through a cathedral [Westminster Abbey (?)](or Buckingham Palace?)], 14
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Big Ben in the distance [Westminster Abbey in the foreground]], 15
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Street in Europe], 16
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of a [Westminster Abbey] cathedral(or Buckingham Palace?)], 17
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Coronation Throne, Westminster Abbey] Inside of a cathedral (or Buckingham Palace?)], 18
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City street], 19
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas holding a newspaper, standing next to Frances Ryan Thomas on a sidewalk], 20
  - Carousel number 22 [Europe; California], circa 1971; 9 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 1
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Statue of a queen], 2
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City street], 3
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 4
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 5
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 6
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 7
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas and Frances Ryan Thomas standing in front of bust of Lawrence of Arabia], 8
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of grand building (Buckingham Palace?)], 9
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Sign that reads "Tower Bridge"], 10
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: View of city], 11
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Sign that reads "Tower Bridge"], 12
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Four men standing, dressed up [as Beefeaters]], 13
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Old castle [The Tower of London]], 14
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Gate [of the Tower of London]], 15
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Man dressed up [as a Beefeater]], 16
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: British officer], 17
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Tower bridge in London], 18
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Parked cars [Tower Bridge in the Background]], 19
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: View of city], 20
  - Carousel number 22 [Europe; California], circa 1971; 10 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of a cathedral?], 1
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: An axe [executioner's block]], 2
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Buckingham Palace? [The Tower of London] in the distance], 3
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Piccadilly Circus] City, London], 4
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [Piccadilly Circus] City street], 5
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Cobblestone road], 6
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Building], 7
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: View of park], 8
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Castle], 9
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Castle], 10
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: [View from a (?) ] Castle], 11
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Sign on building that reads "The Castle Bookshop"], 12
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: British officers walking outside of castle], 13
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: British officers walking outside of castle], 14
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Castle], 15
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: British officers standing in formation], 16
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City], 17
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Road], 18
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Lowell Thomas talking to a man], 19
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Flowers set up on counter], 20
  - Carousel number 22 [Europe; California] [Items 1-12] Carousel number 23 [Items 13-18], circa 1971; 11 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Large resort], 1
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Crowd of people in front of domed [the Vatican (?)] building], 2
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Fountains], 3
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City at night], 4
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: City at night], 5
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Airport landing strip], 6
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Airport landing strip], 7
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Driving on a street], 8
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Driving on a street], 9
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Little girl holding a doll], 10
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Looking out of an airplane window, mountains], 11
    - [Carousel number 22 [Europe; California]: Inside of a large cathedral?], 12
    - Beginning of Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)] [: Inside of a large cathedral?], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statue of a man], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: [the Vatican] Domed building at end of street], 15
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of cathedral?], 16
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statues of people], 17
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statues of cherubs], 18
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 12 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Murals painted on ceiling, long hallway], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Domed rooftop], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Man wearing a costume], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural [Michelangelo, " The School of Athens"]], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Close-up of painting], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural [View of Interior(?)]], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural], 15
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Inside of a cathedral?], 16
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Large domed building [The Vatican]], 17
  - Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)], circa 1971; 13 (Box 1587)
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Two guards in front of entrance to large building], 1
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Mural with candles in front of it], 2
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statues], 3
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Domed building], 4
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Statue of a man], 5
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a chariot drawn by two horses], 6
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a man lying on his side], 7
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of [Caeser?] a Roman official], 8
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a man holding the discus], 9
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a man near tree stump], 10
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a man with a serpent wrapped around his legs], 11
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of a man standing near tree stump], 12
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: [Michelangelo, Ceiling of the Sistine Chapel] Painting], 13
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of half of a man's body], 14
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: Sculpture of man holding a sword in one hand and man's head in his other], 15
    - [Carousel number 23 [Europe (most commercially purchase slides)]: "The Creation of Adam" on the Sistine Chapel ceiling], 16